// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let que4 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "The term PHP is an acronym for PHP:-",
      answer: "Hypertext Preprocessor",
      options: [
        "Hypertext Preprocessor",
        "Hypertext multiprocessor",
        "Hypertext markup Preprocessor",
        "Hypertune Preprocessor"
      ]
    },
      
   
      {
      numb: 2,
      question: "PHP is a _ language?",
      answer: "server-side scripting",
      options: [
        "user-side scripting",
        "client-side scripting",
        "server-side scripting",
        "Both B and C"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "Who among this is the founder of php language?",
      answer: "Rasmus Lerdorf",
      options: [
        "Tim Berners-Lee",
        "Brendan Eich",
        "Guido van Rossum",
        "Rasmus Lerdorf"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "PHP files have a default file extension of- ",
      answer: ".php",
      options: [
        ".html",
        ".xml",
        ".php",
        ".hphp"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "On which Platform PHP Runs?",
      answer: "All of the above",
      options: [
        "Windows",
        "Linux",
        "Mac OS X",
        "All of the above"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: " Which of the following is used to display the output in PHP?",
      answer: "Both (A) and (B)",
      options: [
        "echo",
        "print",
        "write",
        "Both (A) and (B)"

      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: " Which of the following function is used to unset a variable in PHP?",
      answer: "unset()",
      options: [
        "unset()",
        "delete()",
        "unlink()",
        "delete()"

      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "Which of the following variable is not a predefined variable in PHP?",
      answer: "$ask",
      options: [
        "$get",
        "$ask",
        "$post",
        "$request"

      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "Which of the following function in PHP returns a text in title case from a variable? ",
      answer: "ucwords($var)",
      options: [
        "toUpper($var)",
        "ucword($var)",
        "ucwords($var)",
        "All of the mentioned"

      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "Which of the following is not a built-in string function in PHP?",
      answer: "strreverse()",
      options: [
        "strlen()",
        "strreverse()",
        "str_replace()",
        "strpos()"

      ]
    }
      
  ];